Finding Aid for the Edward Ross Roybal Papers LSC.0847
UCLA Library Special Collections
- MAPA., 1960-1962. (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Mayor Yorty., 1961-1962. (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Mc., 1957-1962. (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Mental Health., 1957-1962. (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Mexican-American Affairs, Council., 1960-1962. (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Motions., 1955-1956. (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Muscular Dystrophy., 1957. (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Music Bureau., 1953-1962. (Box 21, Folder 4)
- N.A.A.C.P., 1957-1958. (Box 21, Folder 5)
- N., 1952-1962. (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Narcotics, E.L.A. Conference (1 of 2)., 1961. (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Narcotics, E.L.A. Conference (2 of 2)., 1960-1962. (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Narcotics, General (1 of 2)., 1960-1962. (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Narcotics, General (2 of 2)., 1959-1961. (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Narcotics, Police Department., 1954-1960. (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Narcotics, Youth Conference., 1961-1962. (Box 22, Folder 1)
- National Safety Council., 1952-1957. (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Negro Matters., 1950-1962. (Box 22, Folder 3)
- News Releases (1 of 2)., 1953-1962. (Box 22, Folder 4)
- News Releases (2 of 2)., 1959-1961. (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Newsletters., 1959-1962. (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Newspapers, Community and Metropolitan., 1949-1959. (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Newspapers, District., 1959-1962. (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Non-Citizens, Aid to., 1959. (Box 22, Folder 9)
- O., 1955-1962. (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Obscene Literature., 1959-1962. (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Oil Drilling, Etc. (1 of 4)., 1953-1957. (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Oil Drilling, Etc. (2 of 4)., 1959-1962. (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Oil Drilling, Etc. (3 of 4)., 1957-1959. (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Oil Drilling, Etc. (4 of 4)., 1957-1958. (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Organization Letters Sent., 1960. (Box 23, Folder 6)
- P., 1955-1962. (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Park Department., 1952-1958. (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Peace., 1961-1962. (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Personnel., 1955-1962. (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Planning Department (1 of 2)., 1958. (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Planning Department (2 of 2)., 1953-1962. (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Planning, 9th District., 1958. (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Playground Department., 1948-1958. (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Plaza., 1951-1955. (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Police Brutality., 1952-1961. (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Police Chief Parker., 1960-1961. (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Police Department (1 of 3)., 1958-1962. (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Police Department (2 of 3)., 1949-1960. (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Police Department (3 of 3)., 1957-1958. (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Police Department (Complaints) (1 of 3)., 1950-1958. (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Police Department (Complaints) (2 of 3)., 1960-1962. (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Police Department (Complaints) (3 of 3)., 1953-1962. (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Probation Letters., 1950-1957. (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Probation Matters., 1957-1960. (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Prostitution., 1961. (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Public Relations., 1959. (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Public Utilities and Transportation., 1957-1962. (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Public Utilities and Transportation (Complaints)., 1954-1957. (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Public Works., 1957-1962. (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Q., 1962. (Box 26, Folder 8)
- R., 1952-1962. (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Rabies., 1955-1956. (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Rabies Bill., 1953-1955. (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Radio-Television., 1960-1962. (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Receiving Hospital (1 of 6)., 1962. (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Receiving Hospital (2 of 6)., 1962. (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Receiving Hospital (3 of 6)., 1961-1962. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Receiving Hospital (4 of 6)., 1958-1962. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Receiving Hospital (5 of 6)., 1959-1962. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Receiving Hospital (6 of 6)., 1949-1959. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Recommendations (1 of 4)., 1950-1957. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Recommendations (2 of 4)., 1949-1956. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Recommendations (3 of 4)., 1959-1962. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Recommendations (4 of 4)., 1952-1959. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Recommendations, Universities, Etc., 1951-1962. (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Recreation and Parks (1 of 3)., 1959-1962. (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Recreation and Parks (2 of 3)., 1957-1959. (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Recreation and Parks (3 of 3)., 1950-1957. (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Redevelopment Program (1 of 2)., 1949-1951. (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Redevelopment Program (2 of 2)., 1949-1957. (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Referred Powers., 1958-1959. (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Refuse Collection (1 of 3)., 1959-1962. (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Refuse Collection (2 of 3)., 1951-1957. (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Refuse Collection (3 of 3)., 1957-1959. (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Religion., 1950-1962. (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Reorganization Commission., 1950-1959. (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Resolutions (1 of 5)., 1949-1957. (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Resolutions (3 of 5)., 1959-1960. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Resolutions (4 of 5)., 1960. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Resolutions (5 of 5)., 1961-1962. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Resolutions (Retiring)., 1962. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Retirement., 1952-1962. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Revenue and Taxation (1 of 3)., 1950-1959. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Revenue and Taxation (2 of 3)., 1959-1962. (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Revenue and Taxation (3 of 3)., 1959-1962. (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Right of Way and Land., 1957-1960. (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Right to Work., 1958. (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Roybal, Personal (1 of 2)., 1956-1962. (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Roybal, Personal (2 of 2)., 1950-1957. (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Roybal, Washington Appointment., 1960-1961. (Box 31, Folder 3)
- S., 1954-1962. (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Salaries., 1951-1956. (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Salaries and Wages (1 of 2)., 1959-1962. (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Salaries and Wages (2 of 2)., 1956-1959. (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Salk Institute., 1962. (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Salvation Army., 1959-1962. (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Sanitation Bureau., 1950-1962. (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Scholarships., 1954-1962. (Box 32, Folder 4)
- School Tax., 1956-1958. (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Schools, General., 1960-1962. (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Schools, In District., 1953-1959. (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Schools, Religious Sponsored., 1958-1959. (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Segregation., 1953-1956. (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Senior Citizens (1 of 2)., 1959-1962. (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Senior Citizens (2 of 2)., 1956-1959. (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Sewage Matters (1 of 2)., 1954-1957. (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Sewage Matters (2 of 2)., 1954-1955. (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Sewers., 1957-1962. (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Shopping Carts (Cartnappers)., 1960-1961. (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Sidewalks., 1949-1962. (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Sister City (1 of 2)., 1962. (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Sister City (2 of 2)., 1961-1962. (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Social Service (1 of 4)., 1950-1962. (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Social Service (2 of 4)., 1959. (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Social Service (3 of 4)., 1959. (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Social Service (4 of 4)., 1957-1959. (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Solicitations., 1958-1960. (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Solicitations, Current., 1962. (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Solicitations, Ordinance (1 of 2)., 1959-1962. (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Solicitations, Ordinance (2 of 2)., 1959. (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Speeches (1 of 3)., 1959-1962. (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Speeches (2 of 3)., 1958-1960. (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Speeches (3 of 3)., 1949-1959. (Box 35, Folder 1)
- State Legislature., 1957. (Box 35, Folder 2)
- State, County, and Federal Affairs (1 of 3)., 1955-1962. (Box 35, Folder 3)
- State, County, and Federal Affairs (2 of 3)., 1961-1962. (Box 35, Folder 4)
- State, County, and Federal Affairs (3 of 3)., 1959-1961. (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Storm Drains (1 of 2)., 1949-1956. (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Storm Drains (2 of 2)., 1957-1962. (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Street Design., 1949-1955. (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Street Lighting (1 of 2)., 1959-1962. (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Street Lighting (2 of 2)., 1950-1958. (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Street Maintenance (1 of 6)., 1957-1961. (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Street Maintenance (2 of 6)., 1961-1962. (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Street Maintenance (3 of 6)., 1961-1962. (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Street Maintenance (4 of 6)., 1949-1957. (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Street Maintenance (5 of 6)., 1957-1959. (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Street Maintenance (6 of 6)., 1957-1959. (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Street Tree Division., 1958-1962. (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Students., 1950-1962. (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Suicide Prevention Center., 1960-1962. (Box 37, Folder 5)
- T., 1957-1962. (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Telegrams and Telephone Info., 1962. (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Television., 1957-1962. (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Tenth Council District., 1961. (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Thanks (1 of 2)., 1959-1962. (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Thanks (2 of 2)., 1951-1959. (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Traffic (1 of 3)., 1949-1956. (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Traffic (2 of 3)., 1959-1961. (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Traffic (3 of 3)., 1957-1962. (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Traffic (Boulevard Stops)., 1952-1958. (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Traffic (Crosswalks) (1 of 2)., 1953-1962. (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Traffic (Crosswalks) (2 of 2)., 1953-1962. (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Traffic (Loading Zones)., 1953-1962. (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Traffic (Parking) (1 of 4)., 1953-1956. (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Traffic (Parking) (2 of 4)., 1957-1559. (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Traffic (Parking) (3 of 4)., 1959-1962. (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Traffic (Parking) (4 of 4)., 1959-1962. (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Traffic (Parking Lots)., 1956-1958. (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Traffic (Parking Off Street)., 1957-1960. (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Traffic (Signals) (1 of 5)., 1957-1959. (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Traffic (Signals) (2 of 5)., 1950-1957. (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Traffic (Signals) (3 of 5)., 1952-1954. (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Traffic (Signals) (4 of 5)., 1957-1962. (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Traffic (Signals) (5 of 5)., 1958-1961. (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Transportation (1 of 2)., 1960-1962. (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Transportation (2 of 2)., 1959-1960. (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Trees., 1950-1955. (Box 41, Folder 3)
- U., 1954-1962. (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Unemployment., 1957-1959. (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Unions, Labor., 1960-1962. (Box 41, Folder 6)
- United Nations., 1949-1955. (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Urban Renewal (1 of 4)., 1959-1962. (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Urban Renewal (2 of 4)., 1958-1961. (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Urban Renewal (3 of 4)., 1959-1961. (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Urban Renewal (4 of 4)., 1957-1961. (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Urban Renewal (Boyle Heights)., 1958-1962. (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Urban Renewal (Ninth District)., 1958-1960. (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Urban Renewal (Temple Street)., 1958-1962. (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Urban Renewal (Trinity, Naomi, Stanford Project)., 1957-1962. (Box 42, Folder 5)
- V., 1953-1961. (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Vacation of Streets, Alleys., 1951-1962. (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Valley Matters., 1959-1962. (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Veterans Affairs., 1958-1962. (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Veterans Affairs and Public Housing., 1949-1955. (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Vice., 1961. (Box 42, Folder 11)
- W., 1957-1962. (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Water and Power., 1955-1962. (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Welfare Council., 1956-1957. (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Welfare Planning (1 of 5)., 1960-1962. (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Welfare Planning (2 of 5)., 1957-1962. (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Welfare Planning (3 of 5)., 1958-1960. (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Welfare Planning (4 of 5)., 1958-1959. (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Welfare Planning (5 of 5)., 1957-1958. (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Whitman Center., Undated. (Box 43, Folder 8)
- World Affairs Council., 1957-1962. (Box 43, Folder 9)
- XYZ., 1957-1961. (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Youth (1 of 2)., 1962. (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Youth (2 of 2)., 1959-1962. (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Youth Conference, White House., 1959-1960. (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Youth Problems (1 of 2)., 1958-1959. (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Youth Problems (2 of 2)., 1955-1958. (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Zone Variance., 1950-1956. (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Zoning (1 of 2)., 1960-1962. (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Zoning (2 of 2)., 1957-1962. (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Zoning (Ninth District)., 1958-1961. (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Zoo., 1957-1962. (Box 45, Folder 3)